where.com 2010-09-28

# Privacy Policy | WHERE

**About the Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy describes how personal information is collected, used and disclosed when you visit and use our Website located at www.where.com (the “Website”) and the WHERE® mobiles services (“WHERE”) provided by Where, Inc. (“we”, or “us”) and accessed through your mobile device. Please read this notice very carefully.

By using WHERE, you represent that you are at least 14 years old or older and consent to the privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy, as may be modified by us from time to time.

**Personally Identifying Information**  
As used herein, the term “personal identifying information” means information that specifically identifies an individual (such as a name, address, telephone number, mobile number, e-mail address, or other account number), and information about that individual’s location or activities, when directly linked to personally identifiable information. Personally identifying information also includes demographic information such as date of birth, gender, geographic area and preferences when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies you.

All information that registered users opt to provide to Where, Inc. for the purpose of creating a User Profile is stored. However, this information will not be used for any other purpose other than for the User Profiles. We will not sell, market, or divulge this information to any third-party.

Personally identifying information does not include “aggregate” information, which is data we collect about the use of WHERE or about a group or category of products, services or users, from which individual identities or other personally identifying information has been removed. In other words, information about how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and our users’ needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor our Website. This Privacy Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information.

**Gathering of Personally Identifying Information**  
The amount and type of information that Where, Inc. gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, users who sign up to use WHERE may opt to provide an email address for alerts and notifications. In each case, Where, Inc. collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the user’s interaction with WHERE. Users always have the option to refuse to supply personally identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain WHERE-related activities.

WHERE is not intended for use by children under 14. If you believe that a child has provided Where, Inc. with personally identifiable information without the consent of his or her parent or guardian, please contact us at support@where.com. If Where, Inc. becomes aware that a child under age 14 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete such information.

**Use of Information**  
We may collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us which may contain personally identifying information. For instance, from time to time we may collect demographic, contact or other personal information you provide in connection with your participation in surveys, sweepstakes, contests, games, promotional offers, and other activities. However, Where, Inc. does not disclose such personally identifying information to any third parties.

We may also collect statistics about the behavior of WHERE users. For instance, Where, Inc. may monitor the most popular WHERE services and display an aggregated view of this information publicly or provide it to others. We treat this information as personally identifying information if we combine it with or link it to any of the identifying information mentioned above.

We do not associate personally identifiable information with location data unless you have provided your express permission for us to do so – e.g., registering for the WHERE’s My Phone service.

We do not collect, maintain or track your location history.  We do not enable or allow location tracking in any form. We do store ‘last known location’ on your mobile device, but only to establish a location context when you launch WHERE.

You understand that when you use WHERE, certain information that you post on www.where.com or provide through WHERE may be shared with other users and posted on publicly available portions of WHERE, including without limitation your profile, comments, and photographs. In addition, you should be aware that (i) Location Data and other information that you post on www.where.com and WHERE that are not designated as private may be publicly available and can potentially be viewed by anyone.

Aggregate information and Location Data may be shared with carriers, Service Providers and other third parties in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy. If the Location Data is shared with carriers, Service Providers and other third parties then it will be done so in a way to keep your anonymity. Location Data will not be shared in such a way as to be personally identifiable.

**Protection of Certain Personally Identifying Information**  
Where, Inc.takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information.

In some cases we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Where, Inc. or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Where, Inc. goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of  Where, Inc. may continue to use your personally identifying and non-personally identifying information only as set forth in this Privacy Policy. Otherwise, Where, Inc. will never rent or sell potentially personally identifying or personally identifying information to anyone.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations or as described above, Where, Inc. discloses potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Where, Inc. believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Where, Inc., third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of WHERE and have supplied your email address, Where, Inc. may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Where, Inc. and our products.  
For users outside the United States, please note that any personally identifiable information you provide to Where, Inc. will be transferred out of your country and into the United States. You consent to such transfer through your use WHERE. You also warrant that you have the right to transfer such information outside your country and into the United States.

**Links to Third Party Websites**  
This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by Where, Inc. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Where, Inc. does not own or control, or employees that Where, Inc. does not manage. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party may be subject to the privacy policies of those third-parties, if any. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party websites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally identifying information, and Where, Inc. shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally identifying information by any third party.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Where, Inc. uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of the Website, and their WHERE access preferences. If we combine cookies with or link them to any of the personally identifying information, we would treat this information as personally indentifying information. If you wish to block, erase, or be warned of cookies, please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn about these functions. www.where.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Website, with the drawback that certain features of www.where.com may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

We use temporary “session” cookies to maintain information we need to have in order for you to browse from page to page. Session cookies are temporary and disappear after you close your browser. We use “persistent” cookies to give you a more personalized browsing experience and to help you navigate the Website more efficiently. Persistent cookies remain after you close your browser and may be used by your browser during subsequent visits to the Website. In all cases in which cookies are used, the cookie will not collect personally identifiable information except with your explicit permission. You can prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or disable cookies altogether by accessing your browser’s preferences menu. If you choose to disable cookies altogether, you can use the Website but some features of the Website may not function properly.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Where, Inc.reserves the right to change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do then we’ll notify you by posting the amended policy on www.where.com. In all cases, use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. Your use of WHERE following the posting of such changes or revised statement shall constitute your consent to any changes in our privacy practices, and you expressly waive any right to notice of such changes. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you visit www.where.com to make sure that you understand how any information you provide will be used.
